knowyourgst.com 2019-07-30

# KnowYourGST|Tax laws simplified

We use cookies to provide you a long session at website. We do not use any cookie to track your personal information, neither we share your personal information stored with us with any third party. Cookie we store at your system is related to your login and sign up on this website. 

We use third party application to track visitors on our site. We are using Google Analytics to track visitors count on our website. Google analytics has it's own policy, and you can check their cookie and privacy policy at this [link](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245). 

We also use Google Adsense program to show ads to visitors. These ads are based on website nature or interest of user. We also use third party advertisements on knowyourgst.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Banglore real estate ads to someone in Banglore, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into accounts. 

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

## What data we store?

We store your Email Id and password and other information that you provide to us for login to our site or to use any of our services. We also store your data when you use our invoicing application and other services available on this website. 

## How we secure your data?

We do not share your data with any third party, your data is securely transmitted using SSL certificate. Only you can have access to your data. We store your data in ISO certified data center and backup it on weekly basis. 

## What we do with your data?

We use your data to enable login functionality so that you can access full services on KnowyourGST. We also use your data to send you marketing emails, account notification and contact you.

## How do you excercise your right to be forgotton?

You can contact us through contact form. We will delete your personal information stored with us. However data contributed by you on Articles, QA or ACTs will not be deleted. But we ensure you that same data will be available under guest account and your details will be deleted. 

## Other details

We are not responsible for any of your action taken based on information provided on this website. Website may contain links to third party websites and we are not responsible for any of your action on that website. We are not responsible for spam you get on email or contact details provided by you in QA, Articles or Acts section. You are required to submit your contact details only for authentication purpose. You will be responsible for your action. 

Terms and Conditions

Visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at this link.

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy. We will update it here with date.
